

32 years old Based in Questembert (Brittany, France)

### Contact

→ chloethomas.me

→ linkedin

→ chloe.thomas@netc.fr

→ +336 95 53 34 42

## Languages

French → native

English → fluent

German → proficient

# Chloé Thomas

# Web Developer

With nearly three years of experience as a web developer specializing in front-end, I create modern solutions that blend design and performance. My back-end experience complements my skills and enables me to take on web projects in their entirety.

## **Work Experience**

from June

Freelance Web Developer

2024

Creation of showcase websites, e-commerce sites, and

web applications

June 2022 → May 2024 Web Developer - Sports-Village (Vannes, France)

UX/UI redesign of the platform, creation of a dashboard,

maintenance

April 2022 → June 2022 Web Developer Intern - Sports-Village (Vannes, France)

Development of the quote generation feature

2019 → 2021 Freelance Translator

Technical translation (English and German into French):

European standards, press releases, marketing

## Education

Sept 2021

→ Mar 2022

Full-stack JavaScript Web Development - O'clock

School (remote)

React specialization

2017 → 2019 Master's in Translation - UPEM University (Champs-sur-

Marne, France)

Technical, legal, economic, and literary translation

### Skills

Front-end

HTML, CSS, JS, React,

Next, Vue, Nuxt

Back-end PHP, Laravel

Librairies

GSAP, Framer Motion,

Lenis

CMS

WordPress

Mockups

Figma